{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180447563","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180447563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ga-la-kwu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180452405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180452404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 98aed145-21dd-434c-a1a2-31709128af10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ga-la-kwu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180509590","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180509590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c6b71cc2-f16d-4fb0-a49a-0b785a45d5a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ngu-swa-kwu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180517100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180517100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c6b71cc2-f16d-4fb0-a49a-0b785a45d5a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-ku-mbe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180527243","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180527243"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c6b71cc2-f16d-4fb0-a49a-0b785a45d5a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ga-la-kwu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180531418","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180531417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c6b71cc2-f16d-4fb0-a49a-0b785a45d5a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-sho-yu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180537107","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180537106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c6b71cc2-f16d-4fb0-a49a-0b785a45d5a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_la-kwu-gi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180544040","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180544040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c6b71cc2-f16d-4fb0-a49a-0b785a45d5a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_du-kwu-vyi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180548451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180548450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c6b71cc2-f16d-4fb0-a49a-0b785a45d5a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-po-yu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180568167","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180568167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c6b71cc2-f16d-4fb0-a49a-0b785a45d5a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_nyu-kwu-re"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180573139","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180573139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c6b71cc2-f16d-4fb0-a49a-0b785a45d5a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_mwe-kwu-mla"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180577789","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180577789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c6b71cc2-f16d-4fb0-a49a-0b785a45d5a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ng'e-kwu-te"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180583557","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180583556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c6b71cc2-f16d-4fb0-a49a-0b785a45d5a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ng'e-kwu-te"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180595737","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180595737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ga-la-kwu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180600404","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180600404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_nyu-kwu-re"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180609166","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180609166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_mwe-kwu-mla"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180623266","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180623266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_du-kwu-vyi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180636748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180636748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_du-kwu-vyi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180646648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180646647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_du-kwu-vyi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180652352","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180652352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ng'e-kwu-te"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" ng'e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180662492","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180662492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ng'e-kwu-te"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180668200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180668200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ngu-swa-kwu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180677371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180677371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_ngu-swa-kwu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180685403","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180685403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-po-yu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" yu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180695288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180695288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-po-yu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180704698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180704698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-sho-yu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180709621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180709620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_la-kwu-gi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180714085","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180714085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-ku-mbe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwu"," userResponse":" kwu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180719845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180719845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-ku-mbe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180729049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180729049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-ku-mbe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180767211","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180767211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" b4693d93-368b-4d22-8740-d5c70b62e3ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kwu_kwu-ku-mbe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180788380","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180788380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180792235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180792235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180803174","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180803174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWE"," userResponse":" KWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180814209","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180814209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWE"," userResponse":" KWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180815824","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180815824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWI"," userResponse":" KWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180818609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180818609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180820170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180820170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWO"," userResponse":" KWO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180823664","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180823664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWO"," userResponse":" KWO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180824869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180824869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180825330","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180825329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWU"," userResponse":" KWU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180828522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180828521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kwu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180828735","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180828735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWU"," userResponse":" KWU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180835375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180835374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kwu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180842486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180842486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kwu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180850080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180850080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 962742c8-525e-4dd4-9350-1e373e00ab15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.kwa..kwu.asc.lc.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kwu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180859652","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180859652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 1deaa5e9-82e1-42d8-ba1f-0c9a653e5090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpi"," userResponse":" mpi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180864586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180864586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 1deaa5e9-82e1-42d8-ba1f-0c9a653e5090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180869272","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180869271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 1deaa5e9-82e1-42d8-ba1f-0c9a653e5090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180879909","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180879909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180880302","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180880302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180880538","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180880538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180880858","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180880858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180881097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180881096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180884571","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180884571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180884868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180884867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180885777","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180885777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180886204","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180886203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180889117","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180889117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180889402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180889402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180890259","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180890259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180890923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180890923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180891678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180891677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180892006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180892006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180892281","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180892281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180892599","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180892599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180892868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180892867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180896628","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180896628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180897012","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180897012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180897247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180897245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180897561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180897561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180897795","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180897795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180905027","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180905027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180905324","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180905324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180906235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180906235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180906662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180906662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180909633","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180909632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180909919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180909918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180910764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180910764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180911430","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180911430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180912164","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180912164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180912489","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180912489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180912765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180912765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180913078","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180913078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180913345","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180913345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180916835","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180916835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180916943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180916943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180932845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180932844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180950855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180950854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180956496","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180956496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180964457","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180964457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 99e7c9aa-2a1f-4889-9666-90b20c7bed44"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180971759","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180971759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 89eedcff-ffe1-4097-aec3-e04efb4e5681"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180985799","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180985798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 89eedcff-ffe1-4097-aec3-e04efb4e5681"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180988330","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180988330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 89eedcff-ffe1-4097-aec3-e04efb4e5681"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549180988589","data":{"timestamp":" 1549180988589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 89eedcff-ffe1-4097-aec3-e04efb4e5681"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181002704","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181002704"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBA"," userResponse":" MBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181003762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181003762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBA"," userResponse":" MBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181008681","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181008681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181009737","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181009737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181035031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181035031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBI"," userResponse":" MBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181036093","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181036093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBI"," userResponse":" MBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181040371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181040371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBO"," userResponse":" MBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181041420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181041420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBO"," userResponse":" MBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181047097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181047097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBU"," userResponse":" MBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181048176","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181048174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBU"," userResponse":" MBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181051520","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181051519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mbu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181051695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181051695"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBU"," userResponse":" MBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181066094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181066094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" c710a6be-0626-4b10-a5be-1e069c2cd67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.mba..mbu.asc.lc.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mbu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181109456","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181109456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mti"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181112120","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181112120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mti"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181115121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181115120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mti"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181171181","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181171181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mku"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181175828","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181175828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mku"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181178728","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181178726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mku"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181191625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181191625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mku"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181221088","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181221088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mla"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181222963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181222963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mla"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181224839","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181224839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mla"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181235734","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181235734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mpa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181238801","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181238801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mpa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181242391","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181242391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mpa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181252709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181252709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mvu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181255744","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181255744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mvu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181259316","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181259316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mvu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181268041","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181268041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181270805","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181270805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181273728","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181273728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181285356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181285356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mte"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181288743","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181288743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mte"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181292161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181292161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mte"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181313992","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181313992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mre"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181317353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181317353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mre"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181319400","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181319399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mre"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181330100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181330099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nge"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181332960","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181332960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nge"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181334515","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181334514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nge"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181348948","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181348948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181351586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181351586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181354215","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181354215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.3ch..3ch..6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181363307","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181363305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_nya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181406367","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181406367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 07c3b4b4-40a1-4590-925e-8ce5d3686586"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.3ch..3ch..6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_nya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181432289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181432289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 844f8aad-7d52-4d0e-ae47-36f56be39751"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181438810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181438810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 844f8aad-7d52-4d0e-ae47-36f56be39751"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nja_mwo-vya-nja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181448139","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181448139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 844f8aad-7d52-4d0e-ae47-36f56be39751"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mta_nji-mno-mta"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mta"," userResponse":" mta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181456117","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181456117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 844f8aad-7d52-4d0e-ae47-36f56be39751"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_thi_njo-swa-thi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" thi"," userResponse":" thi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181461911","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181461911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 844f8aad-7d52-4d0e-ae47-36f56be39751"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_mgo-mke-mki"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181469502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181469501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 844f8aad-7d52-4d0e-ae47-36f56be39751"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndu_ndu-chi-nyi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndu"," userResponse":" ndu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181476389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181476389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 844f8aad-7d52-4d0e-ae47-36f56be39751"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_bwa-nji-mfa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181481667","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181481667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 844f8aad-7d52-4d0e-ae47-36f56be39751"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpi"," userResponse":" mpi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181488090","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181488090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 844f8aad-7d52-4d0e-ae47-36f56be39751"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mzu_mme-dha-mzu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mzu"," userResponse":" mzu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181494434","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181494434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 844f8aad-7d52-4d0e-ae47-36f56be39751"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mgu_nje-nja-mgu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mgu"," userResponse":" mgu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549181500665","data":{"timestamp":" 1549181500665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_105358"," gameId":" 844f8aad-7d52-4d0e-ae47-36f56be39751"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mgu_nje-nja-mgu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}